



Hi I am an enthusiastic student researching deep learning and computer vision. I also enjoy building defi apps. But for the forseeable future I expect to read and review state-of-the-art deep learning papers, implement them in PyTorch and conduct my own research:)

Professional Experience

Machine Learning Intern Pintel Inc. | June 2019 - August 2019

Hyperparameter Tuning of CNN weather recognition model & Data preprocessing

Backend Engineer Pairy | April 2021 - July 2021

Node.js, MySQL, AWS

Data Science Intern Miragesoft (VR) | July 2021 - August 2021

Co-Founder XREAL | September 2021 - February 2022

Metaverse club based at Seoul National University

Education

B.S. in Computer Science Georgia Tech at Atlanta | Present

Visitng Student in Electrical & Computer Engineering Seoul National University at Gwanak

Key Skills

- PyTorch
- Computer Vision
- Deep Learning Research
- Rust
- Solidity